

\bowtie

mohanamathivanan312@gmail.com

8610664453



Madurai, India

in

linkedin.com/in/mohanapriya -mathivanan-081735154

github.com/priyaezhil3221

SKILLS



C++ `

Python

HTML

CSS

Django

MySql

LANGUAGES

English

Limited Working Proficiency

Tamil

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Python Programming

Web Designing

Machine Learning

M. Mohanapriya

Python Developer

Good experience of software development in Python and IDEs - sublime text, PyCharm. Technical experience in supporting applications which use an object-oriented programming language (python and c++). Experience in using Opencv python libraries and Opencv c++ libraries. Experience with Python development under Linux OS (Ubuntu). Experienced in writing SQL Queries, Stored procedures, functions, packages, tables, views, triggers.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Python Developer COSAI

06/2020 - Present Madurai

Python Internship COSAI

12/2019 - 05/2020 Mdurai

Reactis Internship BRS TechSolutions

10/2019 - 12/2019 Chennai

ORGANIZATIONS

COSAI SMART AI SOLUTION (12/2019 - Present)

Pyhton Developer

CERTIFICATES

Certified on Data Science, Machine Learning, Data Analystics, python and R in udemy (07/2019)

Certified on Microsoft certification program in ASP.Net.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Had done my project on Inventory Management System using Visual Studio 2013 and Sql Server

Had developed the window application for Vehicle Labelling with 14 classification using python and tkinter.

Had done my ML project on vehicle classification and detection with 10 categories of vehicles using YOLOv4's architecture which is composed of Darknet53 as a backbone and python and opency c++

On Developing the ML project on Automatic Number Plate Recognition (ANPR) is a highly accurate system capable of reading vehicle number plates without human intervention through the use of high speed image capture with supporting illumination, detection of characters within the images provided, verification of the character sequences as being those from a vehicle license plate, character recognition to convert image to text

EDUCATION

MCA - Master of Computer Application Thiagarajar College of Engineering

06/2017 - 05/2020 Madurai

BCA - Bachelor of Computer ApplicationAmbiga College of Arts and Science

06/2014 - 05/2017 Madurai